mp3too.com 2013-07-29

# eGexa Privacy Policy

eGexa respects your privacy, so we hope you respect ours. When you use eGexa services and websites we ask you to read and accept our privacy policy which we use, otherwise you will not be able to use any of eGexa services.

The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information. 

### eGexa Privacy Policy contains

**Cookies:** All eGexa websites use specific cookies for collecting and saving information for further operations during using eGexa websites. These cookies are completely secured, free from trojans, hacks or viruses and guarnteed by eGexa Websites Network. If you face any problems with cookies related to one of eGexa websites, feel free to [contact us](http://info.egexa.com/contact/) about your issue.

**Browsing History:** We may log your browsing history of eGexa websites and your activities for analytical or security reasons. We may log your IP address, page url, visit time, referrer, browser version, OS information. We will never publish or sell these information, however If we intended to do so, We will tell you before doing this.

**Email Address:** If you used your Email address during registering with eGexa, it will be completely protected by eGexa and never be sold to any commercial or advertising websites or services without your prior alert and accepting that proccess.

**Account Password:** for security reasons, your eGexa account password is encrypted in [MD5](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MD5) encoding which cannot be decrypted back to the original password. This means that your password is completely protected and unkown to us. In case you forgot your password, you can generate a new password and cannot get back your original password.

**Account Information and Usage:** Your eGexa account info is protected, also you can change your information and details anytime as you wish.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the eGexa service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the eGexa Newsletter, that are considered part of your eGexa account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

You can delete or deactivate your eGexa account at anytime. However some information might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

### Changes to eGexa Privacy Policy

eGexa may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your eGexa account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions or suggestions or feedbacks you can [contact us here](http://info.egexa.com/contact/).

* * *

_Last update February 8, 2010_

eGexa Websites Network,  
Egypt.
